how to pay your sun life insurance
policy via BPI mobile app
we have to enroll first our sunlight
policy as Builder go to BPI mobile app
and log in your account
select other services
[Music]
manage billers and payees
add new recipient
[Music]
select Builders as type of recipient
look for sunlight of Canada Philippines
as wheeler
in reference number input your policy
number
click next and confirm then click done
you can now pay your insurance policy go
back on menu
and on payments or loads choose pay
bills
on Pay Pro select your account
on amount to pay input the amount you
want on pay to choose sunlight for notes
write your name and policy number
click next and confirm
congrats we're done
[Music]